Are you awake?
Wh-Who are you?
I'm a doctor from Chiba.
My name is Date.
A doctor?
It's only a quick fix,
but with some rest, the bleeding should stop.
R-Really?
I thought I was done for.
I thought I'd never see my wife and son again.
Dr. Date, thank you!
Thank you!
It's my duty as a doctor.
Now, stay here and rest.
Thank you! Thank you!
Fool.
I saved you so I'd be able to use you later.
Why the hell did I have to be dragged back here, anyway?
To hell with this!
Wh-Who are you?!
S-Sakamoto, you came back?
Of course I did.
What are you doing here?
Get away from him!
So he had friends with him?
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
I-It's not like that.
Please don't misunderstand.
I just happened to be passing by.
I saw he was hurt, so I treated him.
I'm a doctor, so saving lives is my job.
I've no intention of taking part in this barbaric game!
A doctor?
S-Sakamoto, he saved my life.
He's a good man.
You can trust him.
Nice work, cripple.
It looks professionally done.
He may really be a doctor.
O-Oh.
Stupid school girl.
What do you know?
I'm sorry.
I was just surprised.
No, as long as we're clear, it's fine.
I understand completely.
However, there is one thing.
Would you show me your BIMs?
That will tell me whether you're playing the game or not.
Of course. That's fine.
I've never seen this type on the island.
Remote controlled.
You trigger the switch on the BIM and then use this remote control to activate it.
They're used for traps.
I used to fall for those all the time!
Because you just rush forward.
Anyone who gets hit with traps isn't paying enough attention.
What's that supposed mean?
If you ask me, people who are good with traps are just jerks.
What? These guys are gamers?
They're just wasting their lives.
U-Um...
There isn't any sign you've ever used your BIMs.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Not at all.
Good thing I didn't run into anyone these last three days.
If you wouldn't mind,
would you help us try to escape this island together?
Escape the island together?
Yes.
We'll get eight chips, call in the helicopter, then steal it and run.
I see.
Come on, you really think it's that easy?
We currently have three chips.
Three?!
You already have three?
Yes.
P-Please allow me to help.
We'll all survive together.
I'll be counting on your help, then.
I'm Date Masahito.
I'm Sakamoto Ryouta.
Her name is Himiko.
The man you treated is Mr. Taira.
Nice to meet you.
He was abandoned here because someone hated him.
A carrier!
They're going to start dropping supplies again?
Sakamoto, let's go get them.
If we all work together, we'll have a better chance of getting them.
That's true.
Mr. Taira, we're going to get food.
Y-You're leaving again?
Don't worry.
We'll come back with some delicious food.
Look forward to it.
With these three here, that makes six chips.
The Strongest Player
Fortune is smiling on me.
One's landing nearby.
The wind's strong.
It's getting blown away!
It's heading for the sea.
Don't give up.
We have to get it.
Radar.
Someone else is after the food.
There are six of them.
What do we do? Turn back?
We don't need to turn back.
If we just show them we're getting it, no matter what,
we can scare them off.
Everyone's watching each other.
Two are getting closer.
Two gave up and left.
Two seem to just be watching.
This is bad.
It's heading toward the two who are getting closer.
We have to show them our intent...
Show them we won't give up!
Just a little futher, then we'll catch—
What?
He isn't backing off?
It's risky to use BIMs here.
The first to leave the forest will be an easy target.
But if I'm too slow, he'll take it!
Damn it!
This guy...
He's not backing off one bit?
What's he thinking?
Wait...
Those sunglasses...
I've seen him before!
Ryouta!
Oda!
You die, too.
Where is he? Where's that guy?
Okay, got it.
Damn it.
What's wrong?
I can't release the parachute.
A corrosive gas type!
The wind will spread the gas.
Mr. Date! Run!
Forget the trunk!
Get away from that smoke!
I'll leave the food to you, Sakamoto.
There it is, Sakamoto.
Take it!
Wha—
That was close.
Nice catch, Sakamoto!
Run!
Don't let him get the trunk!
Of course not.
After all of this, no way I'm letting him take it!
I did well to kill her,
but I don't want to go get her chip.
It's gross.
Whatever.
When Oda gets back, I'll get him to take the chip and BIMs from...
What?
You're alive?
It's too bad.
I panicked and tossed that BIM away,
but I should have thrown it back at you.
You only have timer BIMs, don't you?
What of it?
Mine are crackers.
Head-to-head, I have the advantage.
But at this range, neither of us will make it out unscathed if we use BIMs.
But I have this.
And? So what?
You won't let me get away?
You and your stupid stun gun...
I've seen your type before,
ugly girls who carry all kinds of ridiculous crap for "self-defense."
Did you think showing me would make me turn tail and run?
Okay, bring it on.
I'll beat the crap out of you.
Damn it.
These flames...
A flame type bomb?
Another hostile player?
Damn, I'm totally surrounded!
Now he can't escape.
We'll just watch him burn to ash.
That won't do. You have to finish him.
Shut it!
No one asked your opinion, kid.
Just shut up and watch!
But you know, this won't go well.
I'm taking this.
You've gotta be kidding.
That bastard!
Isn't there a beach up that way?
What of it?
That's probably where they'll try to come up.
I-I know that!
You don't have to tell me.
I'm going.
Don't get in my way.
No, I won't get in your way.
Since I'm already so sick of you stupid adults.
What's this? You're shaking.
You're scared, aren't you?
If you need to carry that thing, I guess you must be.
I bet you're a neat freak, right?
Had a bad experience before you lost your virginity?
Shut up! That's not true!
Your shouting makes me oh so suspicious.
Does that mean I was right?
You're carrying that around because you can't trust anyone?
It's proof that you have a weak heart.
No.
You're wrong!
You're a stupid brat.
Maybe I'll strangle you right here.
Wh-Who is this woman?
She isn't normal.
Your stun gun can't help you now.
A strong body is the important thing.
You're tougher than you look.
Just give in already.
That's right.
Why am I trying to survive?
I tried to die so many times.
Why?
N-No...
That's not...
I don't feel that way about him at all.
I just can't.
But...
Right now, whatever the reason, I don't want to die!
Stop struggling already!
I won't give up!
I want to stay with you.
It's not like that!
How dare you, you ugly bitch?!
Enough of your shit!
That hurt!
What the hell was that for?!
You're still standing?
The voltage is dropping!
How dare you?!
Come on and die, already!
Wh-What is that?!
Who's that?
Is he with that girl?
She's still alive?
Are you okay?
That was close.
Are you hurt?
N-No.
That almost killed me, too.
Good.
I'm glad you weren't badly hurt.
If I hadn't come by, it could've been bad.
Wh-What is he talking about?
He tried to kill us both, but he's acting as if he saved me.
I can't trust him at all.
But if I say that out loud, he might kill me on the spot.
Th-Thank you for saving me.
Can you walk?
Let's go look for Sakamoto.
R-Right.
This place is filled with enemies.
The only person I can trust is Ryouta.
Ryouta, please...
Don't die!
Where is he?
Did he run away?
No, he's good.
He's waiting to ambush me somewhere.
That isn't him.
Is he the one who used those flame types?
Hey, there's no one here.
That kid was full of crap.
Wh-What's that doing there?
One of them must've hidden it there so that the other wouldn't take it.
What idiots.
They were so focused on each other that, in the end,
they let me walk off with it.
Don't move!
Move an inch, and I'll shove this cracker up your ass.
Drop all your BIMs...
the trunk, the chips— all of it!
Now put your hands on your head.
He's being too obedient.
You got me.
I surrender.
How about coming over and getting 'em?
Are you scared?
Then do you want me to move away?
Move away...
slowly.
Why isn't he more worried?
He killed without hesitation for those BIMs and chips.
And now he's just giving them up?
Something's wrong.
There's something I'm missing.
But what exactly is it?
A booby trap?
No, all his BIMs are there.
He didn't have time to place anything.
Could he have a remote control type?
That must be it.
He set the trap...
one using remote controlled BIMs, a long time ago.
In other words, that trunk is surrounded by mines.
Hey you, show me your hands.
Turn your palms toward me!
Why?
Just show me them!
Be quick about it!
Fine, fine.
What?!
He must have them.
Am I overthinking this?
Is there some other way?
But what?
Is he buying time while he waits for his buddies to come?
That would mean it's dangerous to delay.
I'll have to take a chance.
You fell for it.
Die.
What was that?
I-It can't be... Was Ryouta...
I won.
What?!
Pretty smart.
However,
I won't lose at BTOOOM!.
iki wo sezu me wo fuseta
I hold my breath and close my eyes
hikyou na hodo kirameku aozora ga
The sky is glittering so brightly
kono machi no zujou wo color
Coloring the space over our heads
tomedonaku namida furaseru kara
I can't stop shedding tears
omoide ni wa dekinai
I can't just push it aside as memories
au dake de ureshikatta
Just seeing you made me so happy
kimi no koto shirazu ni
I didn't understand you
kizutsukete
And hurt you
nobody knows
Nobody knows
gomen ne watashi wo mou
You don't have to give me another chance
yurusanaide wasurete
Just forget about me
The first one to move wins.
Stay on the defensive, and you'll lose your chance.
Ryouta...
that is the only difference between us,
regardless of whether you can understand that or not.
Episode
High Level